<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Skywires on Skycoin Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.skycoin.net/skywire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Skywires on Skycoin Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.skycoin.net/skywire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skywire: The Next Internet</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/skywire/skywire-the-next-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/skywire/skywire-the-next-internet/</guid>
      <description>In spring 2017, the FCC made a proposal in which internet service providers can collect, use, and sell information about customer browsing habits. ISPs can do this without permission. Customers can’t opt out. Being a customer of one of these corporations means that you’re paying to be tracked, plain and simple.
With customer tracking, unreliable coverage, high rates, long hold times and poor customer service, ISPs have become some of the most hated companies in America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skywire and Viscript</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/skywire/skywire-and-viscript/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/skywire/skywire-and-viscript/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Viscript Viscript is a cross platform CLI, and application launcher and for cluster management eventually. It is based on signal library as a signal server, so it can manage the signal clients, like node and the components in skywire. It can be run in GUI mode or headless mode.
Viscript GUI Screenshot: We can add app configurations in the config.yaml file, like the meshnet-socks-server:
 meshnet-socks-server: daemon: true desc: DESCRIPTION GOES HERE path: bin/meshnet/meshnet-run-socks-server default_args: [] help: | [1] Text name of app, must be unique [2] Node address which app will be talked with.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>