<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ask-the-developers on Skycoin Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ask-the-developers on Skycoin Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Coin Interview 2 Youtube Transcript</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/coin-interview-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/coin-interview-2/</guid>
      <description>originally held December 11, 2017 on the Coin Interview youtube channel (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RRjfbR44F9A)
synth is the skycoin representative in this AMA. christian is interviewer
christian So guys welcome back to Coin Interview. Today we are going to have an update from Skycoin with one of the core developers, Synth. Before we get started, obviously we only have two sponsors, one of them is on the show. Ark is the other sponsor. You know.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Coin Interview Youtube Transcript</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/skycoin-coin-interview-youtube-transcript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/skycoin-coin-interview-youtube-transcript/</guid>
      <description>originally held October 30, 2017 on the Coin Interview youtube channel (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BuY5IbkkbXg)
synth is the skycoin representative in this AMA. christian and evan are the interviewers
christian We&amp;rsquo;re talking to Synth, one of the lead project managers from Skyledger, Skycoin, you know what it is. Just wanted to announce the fact that we still have support from ark.io. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in sponsoring the show let us know.
synth Love Ark.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telegram Log - Whitepapers, Slavery and Anarchy</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/telegram-log---whitepapers-slavery-anarchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/telegram-log---whitepapers-slavery-anarchy/</guid>
      <description>Artem Kotelskiy
Hey
I discovered that both papers on the obelisk consensus algorithm were withdrawn from arxiv because of mistakes. Is this true?
Can someone from the team address this issue, please?
Monty Crypto (Xa no)
Mmm, about Obelisk? We have like at least 5 papers about the underlying logic, but wasn&amp;rsquo;t aware anything was specifically published about Obelisk already
Which papers are missing?
Synth [In reply to Artem Kotelskiy]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Want Shitcoins</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/people-want-shitcoins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/people-want-shitcoins/</guid>
      <description>Excerpt from the Telegram channel
 Question： I mean if Skycion is so good I would definitely use it for my business over the rest but where can we see the proofs? The tests and all? Is there a website with more info and data? Is the network already strong with many nodes?
 People want shitcoins.
Bitcoin at the start and now Skycoin have huge education and technical barriers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Question Regarding Latency and Privacy of the Meshnet</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/question-regarding-latency-and-privacy-of-the-meshnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/question-regarding-latency-and-privacy-of-the-meshnet/</guid>
      <description>This post refers to Skywire earlier on in its formation, before it was named Skywire. Adapted from a bitcointalk post dated August 09, 2014.
Quote from: CraigM on August 09, 2014, 07:20:24 AM
 The meshnet is intended to be a nice privacy tool with benefits comparable to tor, but lower latency correct?
The meshnet is intended to allow funding nodes via micropayments in skycoin to cover bandwidth costs correct?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remarks on Skycoin&#39;s Distribution</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/remarks-on-skycoin-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/remarks-on-skycoin-distribution/</guid>
      <description>Quote from: dr blowfin on August 08, 2017, 09:43:24 PM
 I don&amp;rsquo;t get this ICO. Only just a little over 5% of this coin is circulating - the rest of the premine is held by skycoin. This is creating an artificially high price. 1 skycoin = 0.0012 on cryptopia right now. Yet the ICO price is 0.002!!! Good luck with that. There is no credibility here.
 The whole point of this distribution was for the tech VC, whale cartel, and Korean/Japanese whales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin/CXO vs FileCoin/IPFS</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/skycoin-vs-ipfs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/skycoin-vs-ipfs/</guid>
      <description>We have been asked what is the difference between CXO and IPFS.
File Coin has the same objectives as a part of the Skycoin infrastructure, but is taking a different approach. They have three separate protocols:
 IPLD IPFS Multi-formats  where,
 IPLD is a representation language for immutable data objects and hashes. IPFS is a file system Mult-formats is a self describing data standard  In Skycoin, CXO does all three of those</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin AMA Log (held at ark.io)</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/skycoin-ama-log-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/skycoin-ama-log-ark/</guid>
      <description>originally held July 2, 2017 in the ark.io slack
synth is the skycoin representative in this AMA
boldninja Let&amp;rsquo;s all give a warm welcome to @synth from SkyCoin.net and for taking the time to do this AMA
synth *hello
mike Hi Synth
jakethepanda Hey @synth
thrice.pi Hey synth
dr10 Hi
boldninja I think we can start - you guys know the drill. Give him some time to respond (no more than 2-3 questions on backlog so he can catch up)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Developers #9</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-9/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: solix on April 08, 2017, 11:14:49 PM &amp;gt;hang on guys&amp;hellip; so 10% of the coins will be sold in the ICO? 90% held back, where 70% will be used &amp;ldquo;in the future&amp;rdquo;. Can you guys elaborate on that a bit? I&amp;rsquo;m interested in this project, but not while only 10% of the supply is circulating. I also suspect this will prevent quite a few exchanges from getting involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Developers #8</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-8/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: WigitGetIt on December 18, 2016, 02:58:55 AM &amp;gt;Lost me Here: Skycoin has no mining
 Good Luck.
 Response: Mining is a security flaw. Satoshi&amp;rsquo;s original vision was for a decentralized cryptocurrency. The Bitcoin network is controlled by three mining pools. At one point Gigahash.io controlled over 65% of the network.
The objective of the Skycoin project from the start was to fix the problems in Bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Developers #6</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-6/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: esuncloud on December 19, 2014, 05:24:09 PM &amp;gt;We are experts with Verilog, CPLD, FPGA, ASIC, SoC design, and how could we help you guys? According to my knowledge, there is no Verilog repo on Github for us to contribute code.
Response: This is an amplitude modulated software defined radio for the whitespace band. 100 Mhz to 700 Mhz carrier. This is the most simple type of radio possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Developers #7</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-7/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: illodin on May 07, 2015, 12:05:22 AM &amp;gt; Is there any use of running &amp;ldquo;full nodes&amp;rdquo; or w/e they are called in Skycoin, i.e. running the client with port 6000 open?
Response: Yes. PM me your node IP address and I will add it to the default list.
Skycoin has two modes of peer-to-peer connections - DHT lookup - PEX
DHT is disabled by default now and pex is disabled until there is time to fix issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Developers #4</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-4/</guid>
      <description>Ask the Developers - Session #4 Comment: Quote from: JessicaMILFson on April 10, 2014, 02:20:17 AM &amp;gt;When you launch, are you going to have video tutorials, or things explaining this? Because I have no idea what the above means. It seems more complicated than Bitcoin, and adoption is a big concern if there is no way to simplify this.
Response: This is for developers. For end users, you will double click the icon and the wallet will pop up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Developers #5</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-5/</guid>
      <description>Ask the Developers - Session #5 Comment: Quote from: FrictionlessCoin on April 26, 2014, 01:29:41 PM &amp;gt;I for one would be wary about owning a coin on a network that is still undergoing changes.
 The alternative of course is to just wait until you are ready.
Or take the NEX approach of receiving pledges but not transferring coin until we&amp;rsquo;re ready.
 Response: The blockchain security is solid. No one can spend your coins without your private keys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Developers #3</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-3/</guid>
      <description>Ask the Developers - Session #3 Comment: Quote from: td services on March 23, 2014, 04:01:09 PM &amp;gt;Does the above display look right, or should I be seeing some numbers or transaction activity?
 I&amp;rsquo;m trying it out an ArchLinux install now to run it on Beaglebone once I get it running on Virtualbox on the Indiebox stack.
 Response: Yes. You have it working! The wallet gui is running a GTK window that embeds webkit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Developers #2</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-2/</guid>
      <description>Ask the Developers - Session #2 Comment: Quote from: Sage on January 01, 2014, 07:49:40 AM &amp;gt;Why is nobody contesting the obvious&amp;hellip;?
 Endless 2% inflation? And who gets that wealth? Developers? For the &amp;ldquo;public good&amp;rdquo; of course.
&amp;rdquo;- All coins are created in genesis block.&amp;rdquo; (Effectively a 100% premine.)
&amp;rdquo;- The coins will be distributed in a fair, open process.&amp;rdquo; (Fair and open according to who?)
Did we easily forget Google&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t be evil&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ask the Developers #1</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/ask-the-developers/ask-the-developers-1/</guid>
      <description>Ask the Developers - Session #1 Comment: Quote from: Eliavres on December 22, 2013, 03:07:20 AM &amp;gt;Hmm this might just be a game changer..
 Since youre just starting to introduce this coin - for the love of god look at what viral advertising has turned Dogecoin into. Here&amp;rsquo;s something I posted in another thread:
 Quote from: Eliavres on December 22, 2013, 03:02:58 AM &amp;gt;I like dogecoin because it is the proof that marketing, be it by a snazzy name or proper advertising or such, plays a major role in the success of a coin.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>