<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Statements on Skycoin Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Statements on Skycoin Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.skycoin.net/statement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the Skycoin Supply &amp; Distribution</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/understanding-the-skycoin-supply--distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/understanding-the-skycoin-supply--distribution/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Supply Skycoin has a total supply of 100 million premined coins. Currently the circulating supply is at 7.278.040 SKY (~7,2%).
75 million coins (75%) are timelocked (hardcoded in skycoin.go scroll down to bottom) and 25 million coins are currently unlocked.
The remaining supply of immediately distributable Skycoin in this moment comes down to 17.721.960 million coins (~17,7%). These coins will be used to further the growth of the skycoin project as well as to incentivize the Skywire meshnet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin launches trading on COIN918</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-launches-trading-on-coin918/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-launches-trading-on-coin918/</guid>
      <description>Skycoin recently announced that it will list on COIN918, a global digital currency trading platform. With the new listing, Skycoin brings its vision for a better cryptocurrency to even more users worldwide. It’s one more step towards a free and open network.
About COIN918 COIN918 is owed by Australia COIN918 Fintech Group Pty. Ltd. in Sydney, Australia. It launched in beta in 2016 and currently is in version 5.0. The development time has paid off: today, COIN918 offers its users a high level of system reliability, with bank-quality user data encryption, dynamic authentication, and multi-level risk identification control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Buy Skycoin</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/how-to-buy-skycoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/how-to-buy-skycoin/</guid>
      <description>Intructive Guide on How to Purchase Skycoin We have received a lot of messages asking for explicit directions on how to purchase Skycoin, so we are making this blog post to outline the process. There are currently three ways to purchase Skycoin. You can purchase on the exchanges C2CX, Cryptopia, or Over-The-Counter. The Over-The-Counter Exchange is currently sold out, so you can purchase Skycoin on https://www.c2cx.com/in/home or https://www.cryptopia.co.nz/. To purchase on these two exchanges, you will need to buy Bitcoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Secure Your Skycoin Wallet</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/how-to-secure-your-skycoin-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/how-to-secure-your-skycoin-wallet/</guid>
      <description>Intructive guide on how to safely store your Skycoin We are currently working diligently to provide encryption functionality to the wallet. You can view our progress on this issue here: https://github.com/skycoin/skycoin/issues/479. While we are doing so, we would like to provide some clarity on the best ways to safely store your Skycoin. You can download the Mac, Linux, and Windows versions of the Skycoin wallet from https://www.skycoin.net/downloads/. After doing so, you will be presented with the option to create a new wallet once you open the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solar Bankers is One Example of a Company Adopting the Revolutionary Skycoin Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/solar-bankers-is-one-example-of-a-company-adopting-the-revolutionary-skycoin-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/solar-bankers-is-one-example-of-a-company-adopting-the-revolutionary-skycoin-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>Better speed, better security, better privacy – Skycoin offers all these advantages through its open-source platform. The innovative technology that powers Skycoin is available to all. Today, more and more companies are taking note of Skycoin’s benefits and using it to build their businesses.
One example is Solar Bankers, a revolutionary new energy company. Solar Bankers is using the power of blockchain to decentralize the energy sector. With Solar Bankers, users can generate solar electricity at their homes through high-tech, patented solar devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skyledger: Blockchain’s Real Future</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skyledger-blockchains-real-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skyledger-blockchains-real-future/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin was supposed to usher in a new economy built on decentralized blockchain technology – but it didn’t. And it can’t. Bitcoin has major technical flaws that prevent it from ever achieving its original goals. Built on faulty concepts and manipulated to the point of corruption, this cryptocurrency is incapable of creating the new world its users hoped for.
Skycoin developers realized that Bitcoin was destined to fail, and set out to create a solution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Net Neutrality Rollback and How Skycoin Can Defeat It</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/the-net-neutrality-rollback-and-how-skycoin-can-defeat-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/the-net-neutrality-rollback-and-how-skycoin-can-defeat-it/</guid>
      <description>In 2015, the FCC instituted net neutrality rules classifying the internet as a public utility. This prevented internet service providers (ISPs) from prioritizing certain websites over others and encouraged a free and open internet where all businesses and individuals could thrive.
Now, under Trump-appointed FCC chairman Ajit Pai, a vote to slash net neutrality protections is looming. Pai was nominated for a second five-year term on October 2 despite widespread outcry over his agenda.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Built Skycoin</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/why-we-built-skycoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/why-we-built-skycoin/</guid>
      <description>Satoshi envisioned Bitcoin as a decentralized digital currency. Blockchain networks were intended to democratize finance, eliminating corporate control and spreading power among users. However, Bitcoin and related currencies have become centralized due to their reliance on Proof of Work (PoW) and Proof of Stake (PoS) algorithms, as well as their use of mining to create coins. This centralization defeats the original purpose of digital currencies.
We created the Skycoin blockchain to correct these flaws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin BBS: Social Media for You</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoinbbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoinbbs/</guid>
      <description>Summary: On corporate social media, you’re the product. A company controls your data. They sell it to advertisers and store it on their servers. Once you make a post, it’s theirs – forever. You have no control over privacy, technology, or even your own identity. Why should we settle for that?
It’s time for a social media revolution. Skycoin is bringing social media back to you, the user. We’re excited to announce the alpha launch of Skycoin BBS: the first distributed social media platform in the Skycoin ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Segwit2x and Bitcoin’s Consensus Problem - Why Skycoin is Superior</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/segwit2x/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/segwit2x/</guid>
      <description>On Wednesday, Bitcoin developers suspended plans to introduce the controversial software update Segwit2x. The 2x update would have increased the size of each block from 1 MB to 2 MB, doubling Bitcoin’s transaction capacity. Segwit2x had been planned for several months and was set to go into effect around November 16th.
It’s evident that Bitcoin has a scalability problem. Segwit2x was intended to solve that problem by increasing block size. With larger blocks, transactions could flow faster and the currency would be able to handle continued growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obelisk Consensus Algorithm Design Motivations</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/obelisk-consensus-algorithm-design-motivations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/obelisk-consensus-algorithm-design-motivations/</guid>
      <description>This is an archived post from the bitcointalks thread on June 19 2014
 Quote from: yxxyun on June 19, 2014, 02:52:38 AM
 Quote from: skycoin on June 19, 2014, 02:31:59 AM
 Quote from: FrictionlessCoin on June 18, 2014, 09:15:07 PM
 Quote from: skycoin on June 18, 2014, 09:08:56 PM
Development Update:
We figured out way of preventing Sybil attack using a hybrid Proof of Stake system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of the Crypto Market and Development Updates</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/state-of-the-crypto-market-development-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/state-of-the-crypto-market-development-updates/</guid>
      <description>Q&amp;amp;A Summary of the Current Bitcoin Market New Wallet CoinHours Skycoin (DEX) Distributed Exchange Support Skycoin Projects Position on the Smart Contracts Fad CX Skycoin Roadmap Finished First Distributed Social Media Platform on Skycoin Platform Launches Skycoin OTC Market  Q&amp;amp;A  There is no mention of a re-working of the whitepapers. Should this not be a priority so that your marketing that has started has reference material. This is a technical coin and so the documentation needs to be up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Wallet v0.20.2 Released</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-wallet-v0.20.2-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-wallet-v0.20.2-released/</guid>
      <description>Download Skycoin Wallet v0.20.2
This release fixes many of the issues with the previous wallet and has a new UI. While this UI is an improvement over v0.19&amp;rsquo;s, it is only a placeholder until v0.21 or v0.22.
Most important changes:
 Shows the correct wallet balance always. Fixes corrupted blockchain database cache file. No performance issues. UI is responsive. Timelocked coin distribution.  Full changelog</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Distribution Plan</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-distribution-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-distribution-plan/</guid>
      <description>This is an official announcement regarding how the SKY distribution will be handled from now on.
Skycoin&amp;rsquo;s distribution has had a history of being unclear and handled different ways.
At present, there&amp;rsquo;s no ICO. In the near future, there will be a limited ongoing OTC, handled by software.
The OTC will be accessible from the wallet and from the website.
The OTC will have a total cap, a daily cap, and an adjustable price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can Skycoin be 51% Attacked?</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/can-skycoin-be-51-attacked/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/can-skycoin-be-51-attacked/</guid>
      <description>This is an archived post from the bitcointalks thread on February 16 2015
 Quote from: iamback on February 16, 2015, 09:28:38 AM
A non-PoW consensus is DOA, because there isn&amp;rsquo;t enough time to thresh out the issues and trust it before the global economy begins to collapse in 2016. For example, the selfish mining attack wasn&amp;rsquo;t discovered (or let&amp;rsquo;s say widely proven and recognized) until years after Satoshi published PoW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Focus Update</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/project-focus-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/project-focus-update/</guid>
      <description>Mobile Wallet The Skycoin mobile wallet is done.
https://play.google.com/apps/testing/net.skycoin.mobile
Branding, Design We are revamping the content pages for the Skycoin website
We have a new logo now.
Bounty program has been up for a month. If anyone wants to make Skycoin videos, check the bounty program in telegram.
Skycoin Branding Kit
Skywire Skywire is working but is getting a rewrite, to use the skycoin/net networking library.
The dashboard for cluster management (node manager) and global network dashboard is currently under development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting to Where We Think Bitcoin Should Be</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/getting-to-where-we-think-bitcoin-should-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/getting-to-where-we-think-bitcoin-should-be/</guid>
      <description>This is an archived post from the bitcointalks thread on April 23 2014
 Quote from: JFK01 on April 23, 2014, 01:54:50 PM
I guess that Skycoin just want to test the water first. There is nothing wrong with that. They are engineers and want to do testing for everything. They have been very cautious for the development as well. This is something they are good at. Just do what you are good at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Team</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-team/</guid>
      <description>This is the current Skycoin team.
Marketing Michael Terpin (Coinovate, CoinAgenda, BitAngels) and Richard Kastelein (Blockchain News, CryptoAssets Design Group) are advisors to the project and assisting with marketing.
A handful of others are focused on various aspects of communications, marketing and content production.
Development/Research/Management Synth is the architect and project figurehead. He has a background in mathematics and cryptography.
 Telegram: @haltingstate  Steve is a developer and now project manager.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Pillars of Skycoin</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/five-pillars-of-skycoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/five-pillars-of-skycoin/</guid>
      <description>The Skycoin project is a hermetically contained software/application platform, that operates in parallel to and on top of but independently of the existing internet.
The five pillars of the Skycoin project are:
(1) Skycoin, a coin that is better than Bitcoin in every way technically:
 Transactions faster than credit card instead of an hour. Unlimited transaction rate. No need for miners and block rewards. Low power usage. All the problems in the cryptography are fixed (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Meaning of Aether</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/the-meaning-of-aether/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/the-meaning-of-aether/</guid>
      <description>This is an archived post from the bitcointalks thread on May 05 2014
Aether&amp;rsquo;s original design has evolved into what is now called CXO
*Quote from: Tobo on May 04, 2014, 02:11:12 PM* &amp;gt;I noticed that you previously used the name of ether which was used by Ethereum. Now you changed it to aether which has been used by some other people at this forum. Why did you like these two names so much?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin is a Next Generation Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-next-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-next-generation/</guid>
      <description>This is an archived post from the bitcointalks thread on May 06 2014.
 Quote from: -Greed- on May 05, 2014, 04:25:46 PM +1 for skycoin being truly 2nd-gen coin. Bitcoin and all its forks are first-gen IMO.
 Some of the things we are laying the foundations for are third gen. A working, usable coin, with a clean code base and good security, no mining, no 51% attack and a reason to use the coin is just second gen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Coin Distribution Event (ICO) At This Time</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/no-coin-distribution-event-at-this-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/no-coin-distribution-event-at-this-time/</guid>
      <description>We are not doing an ICO at this time. The previous distribution event ended August 31, 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Obelisk: The Skycoin Consensus Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/obelisk-the-skycoin-consensus-algorithm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/obelisk-the-skycoin-consensus-algorithm/</guid>
      <description>The Skycoin blockchain makes use of a novel type of consensus algorithm called &amp;ldquo;Obelisk&amp;rdquo; that replaces both Proof of Work (“PoW”) and Proof of Stake (“PoS”).
The aim of the developers of Skycoin was to correct the major security flaws and “centralizing tendencies” associated with blockchain networks in which consensus is based on PoW or PoS algorithms and coin creation is linked to a mining process. Skycoin is therefore trying to create a cryptocurrency that better fulfills Satoshi’s original vision of a fully decentralized digital currency system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin vs Skywire</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-vs-skywire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-vs-skywire/</guid>
      <description>Skycoin and Skywire are two separate components of the Skycoin Project. Skycoin is the blockchain. Skywire is the mesh network.
Skycoin was built first. It can stand on its own. It was created to address problems that Bitcoin has. The biggest problem that Bitcoin has is mining, which leads to the centralization of Bitcoin. The other problems that Bitcoin had mostly related to cryptography or software bugs, leading to problems such as transaction malleability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Has Nothing To Do With Skynet</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-has-nothing-to-do-with-skynet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-has-nothing-to-do-with-skynet/</guid>
      <description>Recently we have been asked about other projects called &amp;ldquo;Skynet&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Superskynet&amp;rdquo;.
Skycoin has never used the name &amp;ldquo;Skynet&amp;rdquo; because it is cliché and unoriginal.
Furthermore, we are opposed to what &amp;ldquo;skynet&amp;rdquo; from the Terminator movie represents: the subjugation of humanity to machines controlled by the few.
The Skycoin Project has no relationship with projects called &amp;ldquo;Skynet&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Bounty Program 1</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-bounty-program-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-bounty-program-1/</guid>
      <description>Updated August 30, 2017. Remove GIF bounties.
Updated again August 29, 2017. Added translation bounties.
Updated August 29, 2017. Added reddit activity bonus. Increased GIF bounty to 20.
Updated September 3, 2017. Added French to translation bounties.
Updated September 12, 2017. Increase infographics bounty reward to 30.
Updated November 8, 2017. Graphics and video bounties are handled on a case-per-case basis in the bounty channel.
Update December 7, 2017. Add Português</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Community Links</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-community-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-community-links/</guid>
      <description>Talk with the Skycoin Team The Skycoin team is most active on Telegram.
 Skycoin Telegram Channel Skycoin BBS Channel Skycoin News Channel Skycoin Bounty Program Channel
 Skycoin Slack
 Skycoin Discord
  Mailing List  Skycoin Mailing List  News Updates  Skycoin Blog Skycoin Twitter Skycoin Reddit Skycoin Facebook  Media  Skycoin Youtube Skycoin Instagram  Software All code is published to github. Contributors and testers are encouraged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Gold</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/digital-gold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/digital-gold/</guid>
      <description>Satoshi’s original vision for Bitcoin was revolutionary. A global currency that existed above nations and out of the reach of trusts and inflation, Bitcoin should have rocked the financial world to its core. But the vision failed. Instead of ushering in a new era of decentralization, Bitcoin itself became centralized. Power concentrated into three major mining pools. Transaction speed slowed to hours. Fees skyrocketed to their current $40 level. Today, it’s clear that Bitcoin didn’t deliver on its promise of a decentralized, peer-to-peer digital currency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skywire Miner: Hardware for the Next Internet</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skywire-miner-hardware-for-the-next-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skywire-miner-hardware-for-the-next-internet/</guid>
      <description>Sign up to our mailing list for Skywire Miner updates: http://eepurl.com/c4DyAv
How can we create a truly free and open internet? To answer this question, we developed Skywire, the new alternative internet. Skywire is a groundbreaking, novel technology that takes control from large internet service providers (ISPs) and gives it back to the users. Its peer-to-peer model promotes net neutrality and sharing of content without blocking, slowdowns, or censorship. Skywire’s open-access network preserves privacy and encourages free speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skywire: A Free and Open Internet</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skywire-a-free-and-open-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skywire-a-free-and-open-internet/</guid>
      <description>The internet gives us the illusion of control. We can socialize, consume, and do business instantly through services provided by Google, Facebook, Apple, and Amazon. Seems convenient, right? It is – until you consider what you’re giving up.
We don’t control our lives online. Large companies and internet service providers (ISPs) collect our data, track our movements, and shape our experiences. Every time we use the internet, we give these companies total power over us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Distribution</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-distribution/</guid>
      <description>The current ICO landscape is dominated by coins that are all image and no substance. Backed by millions of dollars in funding, ICOs for new cryptocurrencies seem to offer tantalizing opportunities to investors. A large ICO is often seen as an indicator of a coin’s potential – hence the buzz surrounding recent ICOs.
However, the buzz isn’t borne out by the facts. With the explosion of pump-and-dump schemes in the cryptocurrency market, it’s becoming clear that most large upfront ICOs are vehicles built to generate quick money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Launches A Vision for the New Internet</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-launches-a-vision-for-the-new-internet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-launches-a-vision-for-the-new-internet/</guid>
      <description>Skycoin, a next-generation cryptocurrency with four years of development history, rolls out to the public in July. The Skycoin project seeks to popularize decentralized networking by fixing problems with Bitcoin. Over 80 developers on Github and elsewhere have contributed to the project since 2012.
Skycoin is a fast, secure, and reliable currency for online transactions. It uses a redesigned consensus algorithm that improves on Bitcoin, and is the first algorithm of its type since PeerCoin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Distribution Event - August 2017</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-distribution-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-distribution-event/</guid>
      <description>Skycoin is holding a distribution event on August 8, 2017 beginning at 12:00PM GMT.
Up to 1,000,000 SKY, or 1% of all SKY, will be offered at a price of 0.002BTC/SKY (500SKY/BTC).
The event ends August 31, 2017 12:00PM GMT.
Distribution will be done through the Skycoin website and through a telegram bot on the Skycoin telegram.
This event was originally scheduled for July 24, 2017 but has been rescheduled to August 8, 2017 due to uncertainty in the Bitcoin network during this time period.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>