<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Decentralization on Skycoin Blog</title>
    <link>https://www.skycoin.net/tags/decentralization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Decentralization on Skycoin Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.skycoin.net/tags/decentralization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting to Where We Think Bitcoin Should Be</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/getting-to-where-we-think-bitcoin-should-be/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/getting-to-where-we-think-bitcoin-should-be/</guid>
      <description>This is an archived post from the bitcointalks thread on April 23 2014
 Quote from: JFK01 on April 23, 2014, 01:54:50 PM
I guess that Skycoin just want to test the water first. There is nothing wrong with that. They are engineers and want to do testing for everything. They have been very cautious for the development as well. This is something they are good at. Just do what you are good at.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Meaning of Aether</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/the-meaning-of-aether/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/the-meaning-of-aether/</guid>
      <description>This is an archived post from the bitcointalks thread on May 05 2014
Aether&amp;rsquo;s original design has evolved into what is now called CXO
*Quote from: Tobo on May 04, 2014, 02:11:12 PM* &amp;gt;I noticed that you previously used the name of ether which was used by Ethereum. Now you changed it to aether which has been used by some other people at this forum. Why did you like these two names so much?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin is a Next Generation Cryptocurrency</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-next-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/statement/skycoin-next-generation/</guid>
      <description>This is an archived post from the bitcointalks thread on May 06 2014.
 Quote from: -Greed- on May 05, 2014, 04:25:46 PM +1 for skycoin being truly 2nd-gen coin. Bitcoin and all its forks are first-gen IMO.
 Some of the things we are laying the foundations for are third gen. A working, usable coin, with a clean code base and good security, no mining, no 51% attack and a reason to use the coin is just second gen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Perspective on Monetary Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/skycoin-perspective-on-monetary-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/skycoin-perspective-on-monetary-policy/</guid>
      <description>What makes me the most sad, is that there are developers who bought in to Bitcoin at pennies. They made a lot of money already and very few of them gave back to the community or created something that moved the community forward. Everything is a money grab.
We have hundreds of money grab altcoins. Gimmicks. Whole cartels devoted to pump and dumps. Bitcoin is still in a penny stock and show pony, gimmick mentality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musings on the Origin of Skycoin</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/musings-on-the-origin-of-skycoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/musings-on-the-origin-of-skycoin/</guid>
      <description>Skycoin development started two years after Bitcoin was released. The Skycoin Project is almost as old as Litecoin. I cant even remember if Bitcoin had hit a dollar yet or if there were even exchanges when project started.
The first version was in python and was completely working. Then codebase was moved to C++, then moved to Golang. So it has already gone through three language changes. The longest working Skycoin blockchain was running for four months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Well Does the Meshnet Work?</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/how-well-does-the-meshnet-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/how-well-does-the-meshnet-work/</guid>
      <description>Quote from: Korean on September 26, 2014, 05:45:00 AM &amp;gt;How well does the Meshnet work right now? &amp;gt;Can it get pass the great firewall of China? &amp;gt;Is there a standard hardware that you recommend?
Yes. It was designed explicitly to defeat existing state-full packet inspection hardware. This includes the great firewall.
There is no fixed port, no protocol headers. There is not a single byte of plain text traffic in wire protocol, which can be used for identification of the protocol type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quorum Proof of Stake</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/quorum-proof-of-stake/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/quorum-proof-of-stake/</guid>
      <description>Comment: Quote from: iruu on May 18, 2014, 10:40:39 AM &amp;gt;A decentralized distributed consensus currency, so to speak. At least aiming to be decentralized. &amp;gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t really get the why. Why not some variation of proof of stake? For example a version where one stake equals one virtual node. No need for trust when there&amp;rsquo;s financial interest.
Yes. We actually have two layers of proof-of-stake. There is the blockchain consensus, then within the blockchain we have coinhours, which are burned as fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skycoin Economic Policy</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/skycoin-economic-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/skycoin-economic-policy/</guid>
      <description>We have been talking to a large Bitcoin market marker about how we can prevent a repeat of the Auroacoin crash and deter speculators.
We have a data guy doing models.
This is the linear scale Bitcoin price over time
This is log scale Bitcoin price, with regression line. When Bitcoin is over the line its over priced, when its below the line its underpriced.
This is the total number of subscribers in /r/bitcoin This is the daily growth rate of subscribers in /r/bitcoin .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clarification on the Personal Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/clarification-on-the-personal-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/clarification-on-the-personal-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>This is an archived post from the bitcointalks thread on May 06 2014
 Quote from: FrictionlessCoin on May 06, 2014, 01:08:09 PM
I still however am have trouble understanding how the protocol works and this notion of &amp;lsquo;personal blockchains&amp;rsquo;. Can you point me to the documentation that describes this better?
 For a personal blockchain, you generate a public key. To be valid you have to sign each block with your private key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comparing Skycoin to Ripple</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/comparing-skycoin-to-ripple/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/comparing-skycoin-to-ripple/</guid>
      <description>In Ripple you have a bunch of node. If a peer rejects a transaction, then to achieve consensus, the connection&amp;rsquo;s peers will drop the transaction and the rejection of the transaction propagates through the network. That means that a single bad node can freeze the assets in a particular address.
Ripple is must more vulnerable to government influence and control than Bitcoin, because control of the network is centralized in financial institutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Skycoin Decentralized?</title>
      <link>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/is-skycoin-decentralized/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.skycoin.net/drafts/is-skycoin-decentralized/</guid>
      <description>To prototype Skycoin, we used a mix of centralized and decentralized components for prototyping. We prototyped Skycoin and the emphasis was getting each component working. Over time the centralized components have been replaced by fully decentralized components. Skycoin will be fully independent of any developer run servers and infrastructure by the time Obelisk is finished.
Right now - the ledger is decentralized, everyone has a copy of the transaction ledger - transactions are decentralized and the transaction relay is peer to peer - blockchain consensus requires Obelisk for full decentralization</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>